http://www.solutionsiq.com/privacy-policy/#CookiePolicy

Skip to contentSearch SolutionsIQ
Search for
Your Privacy On SolutionsIQ.comThis website (the “Site”) is administered by Accenture LLP or its affiliates (“Accenture” or “we”) in connection with the Accenture | SolutionsIQ brand. The primary purpose of the Site is to provide education and awareness of the services Accenture provides in the marketplace. Additionally, this Site acts as a gateway for registering to attend publicly available Accenture training events. We take the security and privacy of your information very seriously.Your access and use of the Site may be governed by a separate written agreement entered into between Accenture (or an Accenture affiliate) and your employer (“Employer Agreement”), which agreement may be entitled “Master Services Agreement” or something similar. In such case, Accenture’s privacy obligations to you are governed by that Employer Agreement.The following provides an overview of how we protect your privacy during your visit.What Personal Data Does Accenture Process?Accenture will only collect personal data about you where necessary to achieve the purposes set out in this privacy statement.Accenture may be processing the following personal data:NameEmail addressJob TitleEmployer/Company NamePhone NumbersBilling AddressUsername or ID for web applicationPassword for web applicationIP addressAttendance history of Accenture eventsPhotograph, and images/footage captured on CCTV or other video systems, voice recordings by Accenture which you have separately consented to at Accenture’s eventsAny other personal data that you choose to provide Accenture, its affiliates, and third party providers in connection with the Site or that is generated through your use of the Site.What Sensitive Personal Data Will Accenture Have Access To?We do not generally seek to collect sensitive personal data through this Site. The term “sensitive personal data” refers to the various categories of personal data identified by European and other data privacy laws as requiring special treatment, including in some circumstances the need to obtain explicit consent. These categories may include personal identity numbers, racial or ethnic origin, political opinions, religious, philosophical or other similar beliefs, membership of a trade union or profession or trade association, physical or mental health, biometric or genetic data, sexual life, or criminal record (including information about suspected criminal activities). Your disclosure of your dietary restrictions to Accenture to enable Accenture to make the right meal selections for you at Accenture events may be considered sensitive information.  Accenture will only use such sensitive information for the original purpose you have disclosed such sensitive information.Where Does Accenture Obtain My Personal Data From?The personal data that Accenture processes as described in this privacy statement come from personal data submitted by yourself as part of your use of the Site.Except for certain information that is required by law, your decision to provide any personal data to Accenture is voluntary. You will therefore not be subject to adverse consequences if you do not provide personal data. However, please note that if you do not provide certain information, Accenture may not be able to accomplish some or all of the purposes outlined in this privacy statement and you may not be able to access the Site or obtain services through the Site. Why Does Accenture Process Your Personal Data?Accenture may collect, use, transfer, disclose and otherwise process your personal data in the context of managing its relationship with you and providing this Site.Specifically, Accenture is processing your personal data for the following purposes:Operation of this Site and provision of this Site(s) or carry out the transaction(s) you have requested or authorized such as requests for certain services or content by Accenture.Identification of ways to improve the Site and make it more effective.Compliance with laws and policies (including complying with requests from regulators).Management of disputes.Audits.Providing you with important information about the product or Site that you are using, including critical updates and notifications.Merging Site-visitation data with anonymous demographic information for research purposes, and we may use this information in aggregate to provide more relevant content.Accenture will not use your personal data for any other purpose that is incompatible with the purposes listed in this privacy statement, unless it is required or authorized by law, authorized by you, or it is in your own vital interest (e.g. in case of a medical emergency) to do so.On What Legal Basis Does Accenture Process Your Personal Data?Accenture processes your personal data as permitted by applicable data privacy laws and its internal policies, including Accenture’s Global Data Privacy Policy 0090.Accenture processes your personal data for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy for one or more of the following reasons: (i) because Accenture is required to do so for compliance with a legal obligation to which it is subject, (ii) because such information is necessary for the performance of a contract to which you are a party, (iii) because the processing is necessary for the purposes of the legitimate interests pursued by Accenture or by a third party (as described in the last sentence of this paragraph), (iv) where necessary in order to protect the vital interests of any person, or (v) where you have provided your specific consent. Accenture has legitimate interests in collecting and processing personal data, for example: (1) to ensure that Accenture’s networks and information are secure, (2) to administer and generally conduct business and (3) to prevent fraud.In addition, Accenture may process your sensitive data and/or make automated decisions concerning you, where permitted by applicable law and/or with your prior consent.Who Has Access To Your Personal Data?Access to your personal data within Accenture will be limited to those employees who have a need to know the information for the purposes described in this privacy statement, which may include your managers and their designees, as well as personnel in Security, HR, IT, Compliance, Legal, Finance and Accounting, Corporate Investigations and Internal Audit. All employees within Accenture will generally have access to your business contact information (e.g. name, position, telephone number and e-mail address).Furthermore, your personal data may be transferred to other Accenture offices and third parties, which may involve transferring your personal data to other countries.As a global organization with offices and operations throughout the world, your personal data may be transferred or be accessible internationally throughout Accenture’s global business and between its entities and affiliates. Any transfers of your personal data to other Accenture offices (including transfers from within the European Economic Area (EEA) to outside the EEA) will be governed by Accenture’s binding corporate rules.Download a copy of Accenture’s BCR. Accenture’s BCR reflect the standards contained in European data privacy laws (including the General Data Protection Regulation). Having the BCR means that all Accenture’s group entities which have signed up to the BCR have to comply with the same internal rules. It also means that your rights stay the same no matter where your data are processed by Accenture.Further information on Accenture (and, if relevant, its representatives) can be found here. Any Accenture entity located outside the European Union will for the purposes of compliance with data privacy laws be represented by Accenture PLC.Furthermore, where there is a need, Accenture may share your personal data with third parties, such as service providers and public authorities as further described below. Before doing so, Accenture takes steps to protect your personal data. Any third party service providers and professional advisors to whom your personal data are disclosed, are expected and required to protect the confidentiality and security of your personal data and may only use your personal data in compliance with applicable data privacy laws.Will Accenture And Its Affiliates Share My Personal Data With Third Parties?In addition to transferring personal data to its affiliates and relevant internal staff, Accenture may also transfer your personal data to the categories of unaffiliated third parties set out in the below table.Category of third partyExplanationProfessional advisors.Accountants, auditors, lawyers, insurers, bankers, and other outside professional advisors in all of the countries in which Accenture operates.Service providers.Companies, contractors, and certification organizations such as International Consortium of Agile, Scrum Alliance Inc., and Scaled Agile Inc. that provide products and services to Accenture to enable the operation of the Site or provide services including educational services to you that are requested through the Site.For example, this Site may connect you to Eventbrite and Ning as part of your desire to sign up for certain Accenture events. Your use of such third party services will be governed by that third party’s privacy policy.  The third party service provider is responsible for its use of your personal data in accordance with its privacy policy and applicable law.  For any access requests that you may have for your personal data which are facilitated through a third party service provider, you must submit your requests to that third party service provider.Public and governmental authorities.Entities that regulate or have jurisdiction over Accenture such as regulatory authorities, law enforcement, public bodies, and judicial bodies.Corporate / commercial transaction.A third party in connection with any proposed or actual reorganization, merger, sale, joint venture, assignment, transfer or other disposition of all or any portion of Accenture business, assets or stock (including in connection with any bankruptcy or similar proceedings). A third party in connection with any proposed or actual client project.Before sharing your personal data with any of the aforementioned third parties, Accenture takes steps to protect your personal data as required by applicable data protection laws and/or Accenture’s internal policies. Any such third parties are expected and required to protect the confidentiality and security of your personal data and may only use your personal data in compliance with all applicable data protection laws. Any transfers of your personal data from within the EEA to third parties outside the EEA (that are not located in a country for which an adequacy decision has been issued) will be governed by the standard contractual clauses or as otherwise permitted by law.Are There Any Age Restrictions In The Use Of The SiteThis Site is intended to be used by anybody who is above the age 13 for the purpose of informational and educational convenience only and is meant for personal use. In the event, that the Site is being used by a child less than 13 without parental consent, Accenture reserves the right to delete the child’s information in its entirety and revoke the license to use this Site. If you are above age 13 and using this Site for a child who age is below 13, you agree that the child’s information will be stored on your device as well as its servers. In case Accenture is made aware that you are not authorized to use this Site for a child (under age 13), Accenture reserves the right to delete the child’s information and revoke your license to use the Site.How Long Does Accenture Retain Your Personal Data?Accenture will retain your personal data for the period necessary to fulfill the purposes outlined in this privacy statement, unless a longer retention period is required or permitted by law. Accenture determines the retention period of your personal data based on the following retention criteria:Accenture retains your personal data as long as it has an ongoing relationship with you;Accenture retains your personal data where it is required to do so by a legal obligation to which it is subject;Accenture retains your personal data where this is advisable to safeguard or improve Accenture’s legal position (for instance in relation to statutes of limitations, litigation, or regulatory investigations).Please keep your personal data at all times up to date and inform Accenture of any material changes to your personal data.What Rights Do You Have Concerning Your Personal Data Processed By Accenture?You have the right (in the circumstances and under the conditions, and subject to the exceptions, set out in applicable law) to:request access to your personal data: this right entitles you to request access to personal data Accenture processes about you, as well as to certain information on such processing;request rectification of your personal data: this right entitles you to request the rectification or completion of any of your personal data that would be inaccurate or incomplete;request erasure of your personal data: this right entitles you to request the erasure of your personal data, including where such personal data would no longer be necessary to achieve the purposes;object to the processing of your personal data: this right entitles you to request that Accenture no longer processes your personal data;request the restriction of the processing of your personal data: this right entitles you to request that Accenture only processes your personal data in limited circumstances, including with your consent;request a copy or the portability of your personal data: this right entitles you to receive a copy of personal data that you have provided to Accenture.Please note, however, that certain personal data may be exempt from the above-mentioned rights pursuant to applicable data protection or other laws and regulations.You have the right to withdraw such consent at any time by contacting solutionsiq@accenture.com. Please note that this will not affect Accenture’s right to process personal data obtained prior to the withdrawal of your consent, or its right to continue parts of the processing based on other legal bases than your consent.If, despite Accenture’s commitment and efforts to protect your personal data, you believe that your data protection rights have been violated, you have the right at all times to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority, either in the country where you live, the country where you work or the country where you deem that data protection law has been infringed.Does This Site Use Cookies?Yes, we use of cookies. For Accenture’s policy on cookies, please see here. For this Site, Accenture uses cookies from the following third party companies:  Google Analytics, Salesforce, Kissmetrics.For more information on how these companies collect and use information on our behalf, please refer to their privacy policies: Google at Google Privacy & Terms, Salesforce at  Salesforce Privacy and  Kissmetrics at  Kissmetrics Privacy.What Are Your Rights Regarding Marketing Communication?You can exercise your right to prevent marketing communications to you by checking certain boxes on the forms we use to collect your personal data, or by utilizing opt-out mechanisms in e-mails we send to you. You can also exercise the right to discontinue marketing communications to you, inform us of your opt-out preferences, or to have your personal data removed from our customer relationship management (CRM) databases at any time by contacting at solutionsiq@accenture.com. In such cases, we will retain minimum personal data to note that you opted out in order to avoid contacting you again.What If You Have Questions Or Want Further Information?This privacy statement aims to give you complete and transparent information on how Accenture processes your personal data.If you have any further questions or concerns regarding how Accenture processes your personal data, or if you wish to exercise any of your foregoing rights, please contact solutionsiq@accenture.com or the data protection officer at dataprivacyofficer@accenture.com.Changes to this Privacy PolicyWe may update this Privacy Policy in the future. We will notify you about material changes to this Privacy Policy by placing a prominent notice on the Site.
HomeWhat You GainWhat We DoTrainingTraining OverviewCorporate TrainingAgile Coaching InstituteScaled Agile FrameworkLearning LibraryCertificationsResourcesResource LibraryAgile Amped PodcastAgile GlossarySubmit a TopicSubscribeAboutWho We AreLeadership TeamPartnersCareersContact We use cookies to enable website functionality, understand the performance of our site, provide social media features, and serve more relevant content to you. We may also place cookies on our and our partners’ behalf to help us deliver more targeted ads and assess the performance of these campaigns. You may review our Privacy Policy here and our Cookies Policy here.Accept
